Hi friends everyday car insurance guri man
so definite like y share subscribe y
video gan me nate so definite video te
informative ga um so chala mandi anar car
insurance renewal ela chayali dani related
information rinchi so akni video chada nakan
so car insurance related information te on
step by step tan so v screen shot
ne sher chasta so definite information te chad so alo
first point koche sir ke ad IDV
value so car o insurance declared
value so ine chala important so ana m
car insurance renewal ki na so IDV
value led insurance declared value
ane chala important so ad m car total
amount a m ex showroom amount te car
ex showroom amount so total amount a t varq ud ane
check chus
maximum limit pe tr ana m vehicle damages a
definite m a amount rates und s u  So we have
high amount la chako chala mand premium sev ekam prakana
takv price ki IDV value
aan so n any major damage definite plus so
IDV value is an important so definite
check next check no claim bonus amr
last year nove
claim ya pata hikle a damage akpana led chi
chi repair dan insurance claim gun then so
definite no claim bonus is a useful at so
company b depend a 10 20 25 um no claim
bonus so again no claim bonus tad and so
no claim bonus wala a premium aan
percentage and so no claim bonus is an
important la mr last company te for
example r ic l d a d a c argo itla
different company te same so indu guna me
already last year g policy te kute year m
continuos ch claim chase no  Claim bonus
and discount and offer chase so in no
claim bonus uda le ane checkus insurance
runal so next point k man ki koni
important coverages ane undaali so aa
important coverages ane m chad so alo
first point chassis zero depreciation so
car loan zero depreciation ane me car
engine koli every year o 10 20 per anne depreciation at
main value and so a car loan u view and every year at all
time low vehicle
parts depreciate at for example
bumpers and main external body parts and
mechanical parts and usage and usage
and product spares
depreciate at value and
depreciate at so internal zero depreciation cover
teesko va bumper to bumper insurance te dan
advantage ta tt parts  If there is any
additional cost then it is zero depth cover and it is
100% cost effective then it is very important then
next part sir, I may return the invoice and if there is
major damage to the car then I may pay the invoice and the
amount charged by the insurance company
then I may pay the insurance company and the
cover will definitely
return the invoice and if there is any option then I may select the
engine cover and then the next point sir, I may get the engine
protection and then the engine
replacement and then the engine parts damage and then the
engine protection cover is definitely
useful and then the next point sir, I may get the
road side assistance from the car and
accident and then the car to the service
center and then the roadside assistance  The most important
points for insurance renewal are the RS cover and the definite points for policy renewal. The major important points for insurance renewal are the following: The cover type is up to Rs.
50,000 and the additional covers are optional. The cover type is up to Rs. 50,000 and the additional covers are
optional. The
RS cover is only mandatory for
insurance policies which cover all the insurance coverage and all the damages caused by land damage. The definite points for
policy
renewal are also counted for different
insurance companies.  If
you are a Suzuki car owner then you can easily
buy a car
from our website and you can easily buy a car from us. If
you are a Suzuki car enthusiast then you can ...  If you are a car insurance
company then you can get
third
party insurance cover if you are a car insurance company then you can get third party cover if you are a car insurance company then you can get third party
cover if you are a car insurance company then you can get third party
cover if you are a car insurance company then you can get comprehensive insurance ...  Important points so definitely watch these
videos and keep watching